有可能就這樣跌個倒
There's a chance that I could fall
就再也起不來
and not come back
也不想怎麼脫離困境
and never regret a thing
改變遙不可及
I'd never get back on track
前方濃霧一片
Darkness all around me
總讓我看不著希望
I can't find the light
任由黑暗蒙蔽雙眼
I let it all surround me
沒試過就放棄抵抗
Giving up without a fight
痛苦心聲吐不盡
The bitterness and pain inside
無數眼淚流不盡
countless tears I had to cry
我曾面對這些恐懼
I was facing all my fears
只為等你替我擦眼淚，但－－
just to let you in to dry my tears, but--
你的仁慈如此真誠
Your kindness won't betray me
我能聽見你的心聲
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要拋棄我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
這肯定錯不了
I know this can't be wrong
我準備好了，請你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
看著你找到寧靜
Quiet grace surrounds you
教會了我怎麼自己
and helps me find my own
不知你怎麼幫的
I can't tell you how you've helped me
亦或是我成長了多少
and how much I have grown
即使你是如此遙遠
Even though you're far away
你開闊了我的視線
inspiration comes from you
每天都要越來越正面！
To shine a little brighter every day!
要是你能知道...
If you only knew...
我再也不會感到失落
I will never get upset
而我絕對，永遠不會忘記
and I will never, ever forget
你帶給我的幸福
The happiness you made me feel
好像你是真實存在般...但－－
almost as if you're actually real...but--
你的仁慈如此真誠
Your kindness won't betray me
我能聽見你的心聲
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要拋棄我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
這肯定錯不了
I know this can't be wrong
我準備好了，請你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
你的仁慈如此真誠
Your kindness won't betray me
我能聽見你的心聲
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
即使你永遠不會知道
in a way you'll never know
你的仁慈如此真誠
Your kindness won't betray me
我能聽見你的心聲
I feel your heart and soul
你的仁慈能拯救我
Your kindness still can save me
希望你不要拋棄我
I choose to not let go
伸出手，你勾住我心
Stretching out you somehow reach me
這肯定錯不了
I know this can't be wrong
我準備好了，請你教我
I'm ready, won't you teach me
你的待人之道
the way to get along
即使冷風股股吹來
Even when the cold wind's blowing
即使我如此想屈服
and I want to just give in
只要聽到你的歌聲
It warms my heart just knowing
我就感到如此溫暖
I'll hear your voice again
你何不大聲唱
So won't you sing it loud
你何不繼續唱
and won't you sing it long
我承諾過了，我會記得
I promise to remember
你的仁慈之歌
your song of kindness
我承諾過我會記得
I promise to remember
我承諾過我會記得...
I promise to remember...